email.com 2002-06-03

# email.com

**Privacy Policy**

* * *

When you **register** for an account:

**_We Will:_**

| 

**_We Won't:_**  
  
---|---  
  
1.  Collect personally identifiable (e.g. name, address) and demographic (e.g. age, gender) information about you. We will use the demographic data to post ads (appealing to your demographic) on our Web site when you log in. 

2.  Provide industry-standard security to protect your personal information while it is in our possession. If you use your credit card to pay for premium services, then your credit card information will be encrypted using SSL technology and will be stored on secure servers.

3.  Give you access to review and edit your personal and demographic information while it is in our possession. 

4.  Send you service announcements notifying you of any new products or updates to the service. We may use your alternate E-mail address and home address to ensure that you receive important information about your account or information you have requested.

5.  Give you the choice of "opting in" to receive third party mailings.

6.  Make it easy for you to unsubscribe from any email.com-owned mailing list by following directions at the bottom of any e-mail that you receive from us.    
*(unless it is vital to the operation of your account).

7.  Bundle information to better design our Web site and to share with our advertisers and partners. This aggregate information cannot be used to learn anything about any particular individual. 

| 

1.  Send you unsolicited commercial e-mail (spam). 

2.  Do the following, without your explicit permission; 

  1. Share your personal information or demographic data
  2. Give anyone access to your e-mail, **or**
  3. Open or read messages in your account:

unless, we believe, in good faith, that such release is necessary to: 

  1. Comply with the law
  2. Enforce or apply the terms of our user agreement, **or**
  3. Protect the rights, property, or safety of email.com, our users, or the public.

We may also transfer personally identifiable information to abuyer of all or part of our business.

3.  Share any data with outside parties that would identify a specific user.

4.  Knowingly collect information from children under the age of 13. [Click here](http://www.ftc.gov/ogc/coppa1.htm) for more information.

5.  Contact you via e-mail or any other method to ask you for your password. Do not share your password with anyone; you should only enter it directly into our Web site.

6.  Contact you via e-mail or any other method to ask you for your credit card information. You should only enter this information directly into our Web site.

7.  Materially change how we use your personally identifiable information without placing a prominent notice on our Web site first.  
  
_**Cookies**_ : Our Web site uses cookies for the purpose of identifying you uniquely. This allows us to pre-populate your E-mail address on the login page and to distinguish between your mail session and that of the many other people using our service. Cookies also ensure that you view relevant ad banners on our Web site when you log in. Our web-based mail service will not function unless your browser is set to accept cookies. 

* * *

_**Links**_ : Be aware that when you click on ad banners, you may be redirected to other sites not operated by email.com. You are responsible for information that you provide to these sites. We recommend that you review the privacy policy of any site that requests personal information.   
** Note that this policy does not cover the privacy practices of these linked sites. 

* * *

_**General Information Collected**_ : When visiting our site, some general information is collected including: IP address (your computer's unique signature) Operating system (e.g., Windows 95) Browser software (e.g., Microsoft Internet Explorer, Netscape) Internet Service Provider (e.g., Earthlink, Verizon). 

The information we collect is aggregated to reflect the population as a whole rather than focused on individuals. We use it to help us better understand the people who visit email.com. In addition, like many other sites with paid advertising, we disclose some of this aggregate information to advertisers to inform them of the number of people who have seen and clicked on their advertisements.

* * *

_**[DoubleClick](http://www.doubleclick.com/)**_ : We do **not** provide DoubleClick with any of your personal or demographic information. We are able to post ad banners targeting your demographic by matching your data with the demographic the ad banner is targeting. It is important to note that these ads may contain cookies. To find out more about how DoubleClick manages privacy in conjunction with serving ads go to [ Click here](http://www.doubleclick.com/us/corporate/privacy/). 

* * *

_**Third Party Service Providers** :_ Agents of email.com may occasionally process individual user data.  However, they are not allowed to use this information for any other purpose. All individual user data is owned and controlled by email.com. 

* * *

Questions? For any questions or comments concerning email.com's privacy policy, please write to [privacydirector@corp.mail.com](mailto:privacydirector@corp.mail.com)

If you need to contact us, do not reply to an e-mail that you have received unless you are sure that it is going to the above address, or any address with the domain corp.email.com or staff.email.com.

Last updated 11/23/00
